What could this guy possibly need
from me I've had a big stupid day and
just want to go home So what exactly
is it you want me to do with you? Hmm?
A sparring session.
Oh, so a mock battle.
I don't think I've had a training
partner since I was attending the schools
You may have guessed but
I'm a big thing around here.
Feel free to choose
whatever weapon you wish!
Let me see what our new big
thing is truly capable of.
You know what?
This is a godsend!
For an up-and-coming adventurer.
Right?
So let's do it!
Asa yaka ni ahog somari
How not to do the world?
Kodok wo seou ta la.
Ukande kuru musion.
Hiru ga esu yoj sae mo?
Na ni wo mii tsuketakute.
Na ni wo kukamitakute?
I'm going to take you back,
but I'm going to take you back.
If you don't want to return,
I can't get you back.
I'm not going to get you back.
I'm going to take you back.
I'm going to
take you back.
I don't know how much of a challenge
I'll be for a legend like him,
but it is a good chance for
me to learn some things.
A sparring session with Captain Gilbert?
Who even is that guy?
Hope he enjoys the afterlife.
All right, let's go.
Such polished movement and the way
he controls his pace is made or art.
He must have trained incessantly
to get himself to this level.
But why is he so slow?
Oh, I think I get it.
With me as his opponent, there's no point
in showing any clues of what he can do.
Time out, please.
Huh?
Thank you for taking it easy on me,
but don't feel you have to
hold back quite so much.
Noted.
What have we here?
He may have something after all.
My mistake.
Sorry about that.
Yes, much faster than before.
But, more importantly, the moment I evade
him, he leaves himself completely open.
It's like he's luring me in.
Why can I not make contact?
Uh-huh.
It's a trap.
I don't think he's really fighting yet.
Who is this guy?
Let's see you dodge this!
Nice!
He changed it up!
Gotcha!
Not even close!
You don't have to toy with me.
You can go ahead and
speed up your attacks.
Will do.
There's no way.
Is he already giving it all he's got?
Did all my years of
training and training...
Did it actually amount to something?
Then maybe, maybe I might be able to...
Drag wave!
Very well done.
This one's my loss.
That was close.
Do you see that?
How could anyone evade
the captain's regrave?
He was using a practice spear with a wider
tip so the wind force sends a guy flying.
If it had been a battle spear
he would have lost his head.
Yeah. Really.
People with talent like captain
gilbert are one in a million.
Talent, huh?
Right.
I knew I had a gift for this the
moment I held a spear in my hand.
Enough!
The winner is Sir Gilbert.
That's the guy you were talking
about in the Royal Capital.
The difference in their
power is clear as day.
There's no one in the village
that can beat that guy anymore.
The more I trained, the more polished my
technique became, and the stronger I grew.
But...
Did you enjoy yourself
here in our village?
It was fine, although painfully boring.
I understand you traveled to various areas
searching for the strongest opponents,
but I doubt there's
anyone around these parts
who can possibly match
you spear for spear.
I've defeated every worthy opponent
in the entire royal capital.
I set out with hopes that
I could find someone here.
According to the latest rumors,
the balance of power between the kingdom
and their neighbors is falling apart.
Right now,
they are calling for more troops,
and people will be gathering
in search of fame and fortune.
Perhaps you can find
someone in their ranks.
Return to the capital while
they assemble new warriors.
I returned to the royal capital and
obsessively continued hunting down demons.
And whenever I heard someone
formidable join the core,
I challenged them immediately.
And I thoroughly trounced them.
This just isn't doing it for me.
Is there no one to give
me a real challenge?
I'm so over this.
Every fiber of my being is bored.
I am surrounded by such weakness.
I thought I'd find you here.
Instructor, you're looking glum.
For someone bestowed
such an honorable alias.
Mr. Spear Sovereign.
Just another cumbersome,
obvious title thrust upon me.
Hmm.
Well, that's rather rude of you.
I didn't realize a title equal
to my own rank was a burden.
I am just done.
How long can I keep
clobbering mindless dolts?
What about sparring with Ines?
Spar with Ines?
Yes, well, she's strong in her own way.
But no matter her approach,
I'd win every time.
There's no point.
You think so?
Why can there not be more competent
competitors like you, Instructor?
Like me, huh?
I admit that does sound entertaining.
I'm sure you must be losing it as well.
Training soldiers and adventurers who have
about as much talent as your pinky finger.
My job is to protect the royal capital.
I can't win a war by myself,
no matter how skilled I am.
Besides, at some point, someone
will appear and surpass me.
Someday.
Huh?
I hope they show up while I'm
still able to walk around.
If I don't throw myself off a cliff first.
A man defeats a minotaur,
basically by himself.
I had to see what that
person was all about.
He showed not an ounce of interest
in the most lavish of rewards.
And while an audience with
the king, ugh, so uncouth.
his fight was impressive of course
however it never felt like he had the
power to kill a beast
of that size and yet he
did why can
i not make contact
you don't have to toy with
me you can go ahead and
speed up your attacks
Careful what you wish for.
He did ask for it.
So I went at him full force.
My most powerful technique.
Even faster than the speed of sound.
Now I knew letting something like that
loose on a normal person, they would die.
But it was the only way.
Right in that moment, I had
to reach him with my spear.
Drag wave!
I had no idea what happened.
For the first time in a head-to-head
battle, I was soundly defeated.
And furthermore, very well done.
This one's my loss.
What did you say? I get it. You win.
There's no point for us to keep going.
Was he showing me pity because we
were in front of my subordinates?
I had been humiliated.
What just what is it you get yeah let's
call it you were great and then there
were his parting words see ya I look
forward to playing with you again sometime?
What on earth happened to the floor did we
just do that I haven't
a clue how he did it?
He evaded everything even my
favorite technique at full strength!
Looks like things are finally
gonna get interesting.
Oh man that guy had an incredible attack!
What was I doing thinking I was
becoming some hidden super adventurer?
I had already used both physical
enhancement and featherstep to avoid it.
If he hadn't held back for a
moment so I could run away.
I'd be dead right now.
He even warned me about pride.
Basically told me what he'd do.
Wow, he's something else, that guy.
Greg?
Gerb?
Or Berg, maybe?
Bird? Or Richard?
No, that can't be right.
Well, whatever his name is, I am in awe.
I have so much more to learn.
Oh, yeah!
This is perfect for scraping out muck.
I mean, it even gets the really stubborn,
sticky stuff stuck on the bottom.
This may be the best sword ever created.
Whoa, he made quick work of that. Right?
He does such a wonderful job.
Just like Lin's dad said,
even if you're a little rough
with it, it won't get a scratch.
Of course, it's already so
dinged up at this point.
Who could really tell if it
got a few more scratches?
Nor!
Can you take care of my drain next?
Yeah, I'll be right over.
It's great that my drain
clearing job is going well,
but because of the big demon incident,
I've had to stop my dirt
hauling job for a while.
And since I can only take F-rank jobs,
when work in the royal capital dries up,
there'll be entire days
where I have nothing to do.
Now that I've got this great new tool, I
may as well use it to try to help people.
I could use this as an oar!
Nah, I'd have to buy a boat first.
Or pizza!
But it costs money to buy an oven.
Hang on!
As long as I have the space for
it, I can use it as a griddle!
But well the problem is the firepower
tiny flame with my abilities the
best i can do is light a flicker at
the end of my fingertip i trained
i trained and trained at those schools
and all i could get was a faint
little glimpse of any skill huh
hello lord north good morning to you
Lin.
You are not permitted to take
on such a familiar manner.
Berg, me most noble lady.
Oh, just call me Lin.
Did someone tell you to
be formal with me? Uh, no.
Anyways, what are you doing here?
Sorry for just showing up.
I went to the guild master
and asked where you were.
Am I bothering you?
No, I don't think I ever
said my exact location.
Oh yeah, that's right.
One of her thief skills is
finding out where things are.
So what brings you out here to see me?
Well, sir, I have a request to ask of you.
It's just, I want you to
accept me as your loyal page.
Uh, what's that supposed to be? Well,
a page is someone who takes care
of your everyday necessities
as they learn new techniques
and absorb knowledge from you.
If I had to say, it's close to an
assistant or having an apprentice.
Just allowing me to be
around you will be enough.
I will cause you no trouble at all.
So if you would please be
so kind as to please...
No, thanks. Huh?
Oh, was there something you were
unhappy with from the other day?
Or perhaps you think that maybe someone
as young as me would be too unreliable.
No.
If you give me permission to stay, I'm
sure it can be a tremendous help to you.
Not to brag,
but I earned the highest achievements in
history from the six
royal capital trains...
Congratulations.
Lin, there is nothing at all that I can
teach you that you haven't already learned.
And I really don't need
anybody's help, okay?
I can do what I need all on my own.
Oh, then my family will pay you a very
handsome instructor's fee. I know.
I don't need any money.
In that case, you can use me
to do whatever you'd like.
As an assistant for requests from the
Adventurers Guild or for odd jobs.
Anything at all.
Don't need you to do that either.
Uh, then...
I'm sorry.
I just don't need you.
It's just the truth.
Please, let me show you that
I can be of help to you.
I hope this will make you believe me.
Now, observe.
Icicle dance!
Hell flare!
There!
This is one of the highest levels
of magic skills that I can use.
It is called Hellflare.
And the Mistblade.
This is the secret of the Thief Class.
The Sovereign of Shadows
imparted this knowledge unto me.
And also...
Divine Slash!
That is the sacred class skill
of a swordsman, the Divine Slash.
It's a specialized technique
used against the undead.
Oh, and also... I get it. That's enough.
Then do I have permission to
become your personal page?
Please stop.
Why is she doing this?
She's somehow mistaken me for
somebody who's worth learning from.
After everything she just showed me?
I mean, come on.
I feel like a grade
schooler compared to her.
It's embarrassing.
It's kind of obvious there's
nothing I can teach you.
But I promise!
My power has been recognized by the six
sovereigns, And if you let me join you,
I'm sure I can assist you
in some meaningful way.
I still think I'm nothing impressive
compared to the likes of you,
but I could still learn.
I beg you.
She just doesn't get it.
Wait, I know.
I'll just show her the sad truth.
Earlier,
you showed me the amazing skills you've
managed to acquire through your training.
Now see the extent of my skills.
Tiny Flame.
The young boy with no talent.
Throughout the years, the
instructors at the Royal
Capitals training schools would
tell stories of this young boy.
However, everyone interpreted
them as fairy tales
created to teach lessons.
Because the idea of that young boy was
preposterous, borderline ludicrous.
As a mere 12-year-old,
he attended all six training
courses known for their
daunting and rigorous
nature at the royal schools,
and he completed the full term for each.
Somebody like that cannot possibly exist.
Everyone knows that.
Even the toughest warrior would give
up after three days in that
three-month-long course, let alone a child.
And I thought the same
thing until I met that person.
Instructor Okun showed me something once.
You said you wanted To teach me something,
my dearest lady Lindberg, have
a quick look at this flame.
The tiny flame got bigger,
interesting, don't you think?
Depending upon the training
that one has received,
even the base level skill tiny
flame can grow this large.
It has no practical use, of course,
for me who has lived 200 years
and has some time on his hands.
It's just a bit of fun.
Tiny flame,
I tried countless times
to do it myself too,
but I couldn't make the
flame even slightly larger.
This is not something that
could be done in a day.
But it requires devotion to your
studies for a very long time,
and that's precisely why I was
so stunned. I couldn't speak.
It was many times bigger than what the
world's greatest sorcerer Oaken had done.
A tiny flame that outclassed
any I'd ever seen.
You see that this is my tiny flame,
and my other five class
skills are exactly like this.
Please tell me you
understand what this means.
Basically, all six of his
class skills are extraordinary.
Why did I even bother showing off to
such a monumentally powerful person?
Just some exaggerated, high
level skills that I've only
memorized?
He repelled those attacks from that
Minotaur's axe with only a single
broadsword in his hands.
He didn't brag about his power.
No, in fact, he quietly went on
working for other people.
If I could put it into one
word, I'd say he's strong.
Not only in body, but in mind as well.
He has the fortitude to live
life on his own, so he will
never yield to anyone.
In the future, I will be in the
position to lead this kingdom alongside
The motto of the Clay's royal family
is, Those of royal blood must be strong.
That's why more than anything, I must
learn how to achieve such strength.
Thanks for the meal.
Lordnor, I have figured
out what you need of me.
I'll control my pride and my immaturity.
Until the great day comes when you
will recognize me as your page!
I will follow behind
you wherever you may go.
And learn everything I can.
I want you to teach me everything.
Instructor
Instructor?
The answer that I am in pursuit of,
the supreme strength
that the generations upon
generations of the clay's
royal family have sought,
resides within this man.
Oh, why is this happening to me?
I believe that I have a miracle.
I have a dream that I can't see. I
have
a dream
that I can't see.
Oh?
See you
next
time.
Thank you.